moving ♪
♪ We're beating Hacker
at his game! ♪
♪ Don't tell me that he's trying
to hack the Motherboard ♪
♪ We'll get him every time! ♪
♪ Cosmic worlds, ♪
♪ Freaky places
that we've seen ♪
♪ We've got the power
of one, two, three, four! ♪
♪ Running in a Cyberchase ♪
♪ We'll meet him face to face ♪
♪ We'll stick together
all the time! ♪
♪ Adventures in Cyberspace ♪
♪ The chase is on! ♪
♪ Just wait
and C-Y-B-E-R-Chase! ♪
INEZ:
SHARI! YOU WON
HOW MANY SNELFUS?
600!
ISN'T THAT RIGHT
PROFESSOR STUMBLESNORE?
600 IT IS,
SPOTTER,
NOT A SNELFU MORE!
AND EVERY ONE GOES TO THE FILM
YOU'VE BEEN CHOSEN TO MAKE:
"WELCOME TO FROGSNORTS".
MATT:
YOU GET TO MAKE A MOVIE?
WOW!
HOW COOL IS THAT?!
STUMBLESNORE:
SHE HAS FOUR DAYS!
COME FRIDAY,
HER FILM MUST BE READY
TO SHOW
TO THE INCOMING CLASS.
IT'S A BIG HONOR,
SPOTTER,
DON'T SPEND THE MONEY
RECKLESSLY!
DIGIT:
SHEESH, FOUR DAYS!
CAN YOU DO IT?
YES,
BUT I NEED HELP.
I'LL BE TOO BUSY ACTING
IN THE FILM.
SO I NEED A DIRECTOR.
JACKIE:
I'LL DIRECT!
MATT:
LET ME!
INEZ:
I'LL DO IT
UM...MATHEW!
YOU BE THE DIRECTOR!
COOL!
ACTION!
I KNEW SHE'D
PICK MATT!
SHARI:
INEZ, JACKIE...
YOU BE THE WRITERS.
(EXCITED GASP)
OKAY.
BUT WHAT'LL I WEAR
TO THE GOLDEN GLOB AWARDS?
LET'S WRITE THE FILM FIRST,
OKAY?
AND DIGIT,
YOU RUN THE CAMERA.
ME? SURE!
WHEN DO WE START?
LISTEN TO DODIE!
THIS IS DAY ONE.
FIRST DAY OF SHOOTING
HAS BEGUN!
MATT:
READY TO ROLL, DIDGE?
DIGIT:
ROLLING!
MATT:
AND...ACTION!
WELCOME TO FROGSNORTS,
SCHOOL OF MAGIC.
THINGS ARE REALLY POPPING!
YOU'LL SOON LEARN
THAT COMING HERE
WILL TURN YOUR WORLD
UPSIDE DOWN!
MATT (THRU BULLHORN):
AND...CUT!
OKAY, EVERYBODY...
LUNCH!
INEZ:
OKAY, MATTHEW...
WHAT HAPPENED TO ALL
THE LINES WE WROTE
ABOUT MATH AND SCIENCE?
TOO MANY WORDS,
NEZZIE.
FILM IS VISUAL.
I NEEDED TO LIVEN IT UP!
BUZZ:
ONE HOT CHOCOLATE!
DELETE:
WITH WHIPPED CREAM!
OOPS!
SORRY, BUZZY!
HEY, IX NAY
ON THE UZZY-BAY!
WE'RE IN DISGUISE,
REMEMBER?
HACKER:
AND DON'T YOU FORGET IT!
I'VE HATCHED MY MOST BRILLIANT
PLAN EVER!
DON'T RUIN IT!
DIGIT:
I LOVE SHOW BUSINESS!
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
WE'RE MAKING A REAL FILM!
(SQUAWKS)
BUT LOOK AT IT ALL!
THE STUFF THAT WE'VE GOT!
CAN WE AFFORD IT?
MUST COST A LOT!
RELAX, DODIE!
600 SNELFUS
IS A FORTUNE!
MATT:
BUT WE CAN'T HAVE
SPENT THAT MUCH!
JACKIE:
I COUNTED IT FOUR TIMES!
THERE'S ONLY 300 SNELFUS LEFT!
MATT:
BUT HOW IS THAT POSSIBLE?
EASY, MR. DIRECTOR!
WE STARTED WITH 600...
SPENT 300...
SO WE HAVE 300 LEFT!
WE SPENT HALF
OF WHAT WE HAD
IN JUST ONE DAY?
JACKIE:
THAT'S RIGHT!
IF WE SPEND THE SAME
AMOUNT TOMORROW,
IT'LL BE ALL GONE!
SHARI:
THIS IS A DISASTER!
WHY DON'T WE JUST ASK
FOR MORE SNELFUS?
THERE AREN'T ANYMORE,
MATHEW.
THE PROFESSOR SAID SO!
WHAT WE NEED
IS A MIRACLE.
JACKIE:
WRONG!
WHAT WE NEED IS A PLAN!
A PLAN THAT TELLS US
HOW TO SPEND OUR MONEY,
SO WE DON'T RUN OUT.
A PLAN THAT WE CAN
STICK TO!
OOF. SORRY.
I AGREE.
WE'VE GOT TO SPEND
A LOT LESS
STARTING TOMORROW.
HOW MUCH LESS?
IT COSTS MONEY
TO BE BRILLIANT!
LOTS!
JACKIE:
HOLD ON,
LET'S FIND OUT HOW MUCH
WE CAN SPEND EACH DAY.
WE'VE GOT FOUR SHOOTING DAYS,
RIGHT?
AND WE KNOW WE SPENT
300 SNELFUS TODAY, DAY ONE.
SO IF WE SPEND 100 A DAY
FOR THE NEXT THREE DAYS..
THAT TOTALS 300 SNELFUS.
EXACTLY WHAT WE HAVE LEFT!
MATT:
BUT HOW CAN I MAKE A MOVIE
FOR ONLY 100 SNELFUS A DAY?!
HUH? HUH?
DELETE:
WHERE'S THAT MAGIC CHARM
THE BOSS TOLD US TO GET?
WELL, IT'S HERE IN THE CHAMBER
OF TROLLS...SOMEWHERE.
DELETE:
YIIIKES!
OKAY, OKAY...
WE FOUND THE TROLLS.
HERE IS THAT MAGIC THINGY.
LET'S BEAT IT!
JACKIE:
CAN SOMEONE PLEASE TELL ME
HOW WE SPENT 300 SNELFUS TODAY?
WELL, I PAID THAT SNOOTY
ART DIRECTOR TEN SNELFUS!
I THINK WE ORDERED
EXTRA HOT CHOCOLATE.
DON'T FORGET THE REST
OF THE CREW!
AND THE FILM STOCK!
GUYS! THIS IS WAY
TOO CONFUSING!
WE NEED TO GET ORGANIZED.
LIKE HOW?
JACKIE:
WELL, LET'S MAKE CATEGORIES
FOR OUR EXPENSES.
LIKE THE ART DIRECTOR,
THE BORGS, THE WHOLE CREW,
ANYBODY WHO WORKED FOR US.
OKAY THEN.
THERE ARE 20 BORGS
ON THE CREW,
AND WE PAID EACH ONE
TEN SNELFUS FOR TODAY'S WORK.
JACKIE:
20 BORGS -
TIMES TEN SNELFUS...
EQUALS 200 SNELFUS
FOR JUST ONE DAY.
YIKES!
DIGIT:
AND WE FED THE CREW, TOO.
SHARI:
AT TWO SNELFUS EACH!
NEW CATEGORY: FOOD!
TWO SNELFUS TIMES
20 BORGS...
MEANS WE SPENT 40 SNELFUS
FOR FOOD.
NEXT CATEGORY!
SHARI:
FILM STUFF!
TEN SNELFUS FOR CABLES!
MATT:
30 FOR THE LIGHTS
AND CAMERA.
AND TEN CARTRIDGES OF FILM,
AT TWO SNELFUS A CARTRIDGE
EQUALS UH...
20!
OKAY.
FILM STUFF CATEGORY:
60 SNELFUS!
300 SNELFUS
FOR CREW, FOOD,
AND FILM STUFF!
SHARI:
FINALLY, I CAN SEE WHERE
ALL THAT MONEY WENT!
JACKIE:
YUP!
NOW WE HAVE TO DECIDE
WHERE THE REST IS NOT
GOING TO GO!
FINE, BUT CAN WE DO IT
IN THE MORNING?
(YAWNS)
I'M BEAT!
JACKIE:
ALL RIGHT! GO TO SLEEP!
BUT SOMEBODY'S GOTTA
FIGURE OUT
HOW TO MAKE THIS MOVIE
FOR 100 SNELFUS A DAY!
SECOND DAY OF SHOOTING
READY TO START
BUT WE'RE WATCHING
WHAT WE SPEND NOW!
CHECK OUT THE CHART!
JACKIE:
OKAY, PEOPLE,
WE NOW HAVE A PLAN
FOR SPENDING NO MORE
THAN ONE 100 SNELFUS A DAY.
IT'S CALLED A BUDGET!
HERE'S HOW IT'S GOING
TO WORK.
I'VE CUT DOWN THE CREW
FROM 20 BORGS TO ONLY SIX.
SO NOW THE CREW COSTS
ONLY 60 SNELFUS A DAY,
A LOT LESS THAN THE 200
WE SPENT YESTERDAY.
MATT:
COOL!
AND LESS CREW
MEANS LESS FOOD!
AT TWO SNELFUS A HEAD -
TIMES SIX,
THAT'S ONLY 12 SNELFUS
A DAY FOR FOOD.
WAIT!
I MADE THIS FOOD MYSELF,
SO WE CAN CUT OUT
TWO MORE SNELFUS!
DIGIT:
BEAUTIFUL!
THAT CUTS THE FOOD COST
DOWN TO TEN SNELFUS A DAY!
THIS PLAN
JUST MIGHT WORK!
OKAY, BUDGET LADY,
WE CUT OUT A LOT OF STUFF,
BUT WE STILL NEED
15 FILM CARTRIDGES A DAY,
WHICH COSTS 30 SNELFUS.
JACKIE:
ALL RIGHT,
MR. FILM DIRECTOR.
DIGIT, PLEASE ENTER
30 SNELFUS
IN THE FILM CATEGORY.
DIGIT:
30 IT IS!
NOW,
ADD UP THE CATEGORIES
AND WE GET A TOTAL OF...
100 SNELFUS PER DAY!
JUST WHAT I FIGURED.
FILL IN DAY 3 AND 4
THE SAME WAY DIGIT!
HACKER:
BRAVO! BRAVO!
I'M TRULY IMPRESSED
BY YOUR BUDGET!
JACKIE:
REALLY?
EVEN THOUGH WE FIRED YOU?
WHO CARES ABOUT MONEY?
THIS IS ART!
I'M STAYING ON AS YOUR
ART DIRECTOR...
FREE OF CHARGE!
AND SO ARE YOUR CATERERS!
MATT:
COOL!
(THRU BULLHORN)
PLACES EVERYONE!
DELETE:
BOSS!
DID YOU SAY WE'RE WORKING
FOR NOTHIN'?
ALL THAT MATTERS IS
THAT WE STAY AROUND THE SET
SO I CAN SNEAK THIS
INTO THE FILM!
THE EYE OF FIG NEWT
IS THE SECRET TO THE SUCCESS
OF MY SCHEME!
WITH IT, I'LL BEWITCH
STUMBLESNORE.
AND CONTROL EVERY STUDENT
AT FROGSNORTS!
(EVIL LAUGHTER)