STAY RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE
IT'S CYBERCHASE FOR REAL.
I'M GOING ON A DATE
WITH JENNA.
SHE'S SO SWEET!
(PHONE RINGS)
HELLO.
OH, HI HARLEY.
REALLY?
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
WELL, SURE.
YOU CAN STAY HERE.
SURE, SEE YOU SOON.
THAT WAS MY COUSIN HARLEY
FROM HOLLYWOOD.
HE'S PASSING THROUGH TOWN
AND HE LOST HIS WALLET
WITH ALL HIS MONEY.
I BETTER MAKE SURE I HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY FOR TONIGHT.
FLOWERS $10,
CHOCOLATES $8,
2 DINNERS $20 EACH,
THAT'S $40,
$14 FOR DESSERTS
FOR BOTH OF US,
$12 FOR TAX AND TIP,
$16 FOR TAXIS.
IF I STAY ON BUDGET,
THIS'LL BE A PERFECT DATE.
HEY HARLEY,
HOW-HOW YOU DOIN'...?
HARLEY:
WHAT A MISERABLE DAY.
FIRST, MY PLANE WAS LATE.
THEN, THE GUY NEXT TO ME
SNORED THE ENTIRE FLIGHT.
THEN, I LOST MY WALLET!
HARRY:
JUST RELAX,
WATCH SOME TV,
AND I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
WHERE YOU GOING?
OUT TO A RESTAURANT
CALLED THE "NEW LEAF".
I'M GOING WITH YOU.
HARRY:
OH, UH, BUT YOU SEE,
JENNA AND I HAD A DATE...
HARLEY:
COME ON, IT'LL BE FUN!
LET'S GO.
HARRY:
OKAY.
HARLEY:
AND THEN, AFTER THE AWARDS,
I WENT TO THIS
WONDERFUL PARTY.
ALL THE BIGGEST STARS
WERE THERE...
LEONARDO, AMANDA...
I DANCED WITH HILLARY.
SHE'S VERY SWEET.
JENNA
I'LL HAVE THE PASTA
PRIMAVERA.
HARRY:
JENNA'S MEAL IS $10.
THAT'S $10 LESS
THAN I BUDGETED.
I'LL HAVE THE STEAK.
HARRY:
GREAT! HIS DINNER IS $25!
IF I WANT TO STAY ON BUDGET,
I CAN ONLY SPEND $5
FOR MY DINNER.
CAN I PLEASE GET A GRILLED
CHEESE SANDWICH?
THANKS.
DESSERT?
I'LL HAVE THE CREME BRULEE,
PLEASE.
HARRY:
JENNA'S DESSERT IS $10.
IF I'M GOING TO STAY ON BUDGET,
THERE'S ONLY $4 LEFT
FOR ONE MORE DESSERT.
HARLEY:
I'LL HAVE THE-
HARRY:
EXCUSE US.
LOOK, WHEN I ASK YOU
IF YOU WANT A DESSERT
JUST SAY NO,
GOT IT?
ONE CREME BRULEE,
I'LL HAVE THE RICE PUDDING
AND, HARLEY,
WHAT WILL YOU HAVE?
HARLEY:
NOTHING FOR ME.
HARRY:
OH, ARE YOU SURE?
UH, THE DESSERTS
ARE REALLY GREAT.
HARLEY:
OKAY, I'LL HAVE
RICE PUDDING, TOO.
HARRY:
IF YOU ORDER DESSERT,
I WON'T HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY,
SO JUST SAY NO,
GOT IT?
SORRY, MY BAD.
HARRY:
I'LL HAVE THE RICE PUDDING.
AND, HARLEY,
WHAT WILL YOU HAVE?
NOTHING.
HARRY:
ARE YOU SURE?
POSITIVE?
WELL, I...
NOTHING FOR ME.
HARLEY, WOULD YOU LIKE
HALF OF MY DESSERT?
I'M RIGHT ON BUDGET,
WITH JUST ENOUGH MONEY
FOR A TAXI.
YOU KNOW I ONLY OFFERED
YOU HALF.
BUT MY HALF
WAS ON THE BOTTOM.
HARLEY:
SO, YOU KNOW, IT REALLY
BEGS THE QUESTION,
WHY WEAR A ROLEX,
WHEN YOU CAN HAVE A CARTIER,
RIGHT?
I MEAN THIS THING IS
CUSTOM MADE, DIAMOND-ENCRUSTED.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL, REALLY.
YOU GOTTA SEE IT.
HARRY:
JENNA!
HEY, WHAT ABOUT ME?
HARRY:
SORRY, MY BAD.